August 24,2023

fajagesa19.comp@coep.ac.in

Computer Engineering Latur, Maharashtra, India

Education

Pune, University Pune, ON B. Tech

20019 - 2023

- computer engineering

- Graduated with Honours and a 8.73 CGPA

Science college Nanded, ON 12 th grade 2016 - 2018

- captain of the cricket team in 12 th grade
- Passed with a 88.15% average

Personal Statement

I'm the hardest working person I know, and therefore you should hire me. My qualities include Hardwork, perseverance, and punctuality. I have lots of experience working with computer technology, and I am not afraid to failures. In fact, I'm such an amazing person that I can't believe you haven't hired me yet.

Work Experience

Abhijaat Newsletter

College of Engineering Pune

 $Cartoon\ section$

Dec. 2019 - Apr. 2019

- Drawn Cartoons ongoing crises

Lokmat newspapers

Nanded, ON

Paperboy

May. 2016 -July. 2016

newpaper delivery

Awards, Grants & Honours

My University Entrance Scholarship (\$500)	 . 2019
My High School Grade 12 Physics Award (\$30)	 20018
Scholarship exam(\$50)	 . 2013

Skills

• Programming and Markup Languages

- **Expert:** python, C

- Intermediate: IATEX, Java

• Software

- **Expert:** MS Access, MS Excel, MS Word

- Intermediate: scilab, MATLAB

\bullet Other

- People person, enjoys being challenged, hardworking, enthusiastic